{
   "question-1":{
      "question":"What is called for an artificial language that can be used to control the behaviour of a machine, particularly a computer",
      "answer":"Programming language",
      "choices":[
         "C language",
         "Java language",
         "Programming language",
         "Artificial intelligence"
      ]
   },
   "question-2":{
      "question":"A machine that takes input and output",
      "answer":"Computer",
      "choices":[
         "Type writter",
         "Computer",
         "Programming",
         "Microcomputer"
      ]
   },
   "question-3":{
      "question":"How do computer think?",
      "answer":"Binary",
      "choices":[
         "Inputs",
         "Numbers",
         "Words",
         "Binary"
      ]
   },
   "question-4":{
      "question":"What kind of language is difficult for human to read?",
      "answer":"Low-level programming",
      "choices":[
         "High-level programming",
         "Low-level programming",
         "Artificial intelligence",
         "None of the above"
      ]
   },
   "question-5":{
      "question":"What kind of words used in High-level language?",
      "answer":"Objects",
      "choices":[
         "English",
         "Variables",
         "Objects",
         "String"
      ]
   },
   "question-6":{
      "question":"What are the 2 types of Flowchart?",
      "answer":"System and Program Flowchart",
      "choices":[
         "Big and Bang Flowchart",
         "Systematic and Progress Flowchart",
         "System and Program Flowchart",
         "Autoboots and Nan Flowchart"
      ]
   },
   "question-7":{
      "question":"What are the three basic operation of computer program?",
      "answer":"Input,Process,Output",
      "choices":[
         "Input,Process,Output",
         "Enter,Process,Display",
         "Input,Operation,Output",
         "Enter,Process,Output"
      ]
   },
   "question-8":{
      "question":"What is an Algorithm?",
      "answer":"English way of expressing solution",
      "choices":[
         "Used to fix errors",
         "Way to run your program",
         "English way of expressing solution",
         "A coding etiquette"
      ]
   },
    "question-9":{
      "question":"What is a Flowchart?",
      "answer":"Graphical representation of a program",
      "choices":[
         "A shape that commands program",
         "A way on ordering a program",
         "Graphical representation of a program",
         "none of the above"
      ]
   },
    "question-10":{
      "question":"Which of these are the advantages of Flowcharts?",
      "answer":"Visual Clarity",
      "choices":[
         "Bad documentation",
         "Visual Clarity",
         "Ineffective Coordination",
         "None of the above"
      ]
   },
   "question-11":{
      "question":"Who developed C programming Language?",
      "answer":"Dennis Ritchie",
      "choices":[
         "Rasmus Lerdorf",
         "Tim Berners-Lee",
         "Dennis Ritchie",
         "Brendan Eich"
      ]
   },
   "question-12":{
      "question":"What function is used to display output in C program?",
      "answer":"printf()",
      "choices":[
         "view()",
         "printf()",
         "display()",
         "output()"
      ]
   },
   "question-13":{
      "question":"C language was designed to run on what kind of machine?",
      "answer":"Micro computer",
      "choices":[
         "Super Computer",
         "A.I Computer",
         "Micro computer",
         "ATX Computer"
      ]
   },
   "question-14":{
      "question":"What level of programming is C language?",
      "answer":"Mid-level",
      "choices":[
         "Mid-level",
         "Low-level",
         "High-level",
         "Basic-level"
      ]
   },
   "question-15":{
      "question":"What is the purpose of Main() function in C program?",
      "answer":"Starting point of code execution",
      "choices":[
         "Brain of the program code",
         "Starting point of code execution",
         "Detects errors in program",
         "Used to design your entire program"
      ]
   },
   "question-16":{
      "question":"What function is used to take inputs from user?",
      "answer":"scanf()",
      "choices":[
         "scanf()",
         "input()",
         "inputs()",
         "scand()"
      ]
   },
   "question-17":{
      "question":"In a flowchart, an input or output instruction is represented by",
      "answer":"A parallelogram",
      "choices":[
         "A rectangle",
         "A rhombus",
         "A parallelogram",
         "A circle"
      ]
   },
   "question-18":{
      "question":"In a flowchart, a calculation (process) is represented by",
      "answer":"A rectangle",
      "choices":[
         "A rectangle",
         "An arrow",
         "A diamond",
         "An oblong"
      ]
   },
   "question-19":{
      "question":"Why is a flowchart required?",
      "answer":"Plan a program before development",
      "choices":[
         "Plan a program before development",
         "It is easy to use",
         "To analyze the program",
         "To execute a program"
      ]
   },
   "question-20":{
      "question":"What is the purpose of #include <stdio.h> in C program?",
      "answer":"Contains Input/Output Functions",
      "choices":[
         "Contains math functionalities of C",
         "Contains database of C language",
         "Contains Input/Output Functions",
         "Used to be the mainframe of program"
      ]
   },
   "question-21":{
      "question":"In a flowchart, how are symbols connected?",
      "answer":"Lines & arrows",
      "choices":[
         "Lines & arrows",
         "Connectors",
         "Dash lines & numbers",
         "Symbols"
      ]
   },
   "question-22":{
      "question":"HTML stands for what?",
      "answer":"HyperText Markup Language",
      "choices":[
         "How To Make Lumpia",
         "HyperText Makeup Language",
         "HyperText Markup Language",
         "HyperText Maker Language"
      ]
   },
   "question-23":{
      "question":"Who Invented Flowchart?",
      "answer":"Frank Gilbreth",
      "choices":[
         "Dennis Ritchie",
         "Frank Gilbreth",
         "James Flowsmith",
         "Rastaman"
      ]
   },
   "question-24":{
      "question":"In a flowchart, Start/End Symbol marks the starting or ending point of the system. What shape is this?",
      "answer":"Oval shape",
      "choices":[
         "Oval shape",
         "Rectangle shape",
         "Diamond shape",
         "Circle shape"
      ]
   },
   "question-25":{
      "question":"In a flowchart, A Decision symbol is represented by what shape?",
      "answer":"Diamond shape",
      "choices":[
         "Diamond shape",
         "Rectangle shape",
         "Pill shape",
         "Arrows"
      ]
   },
   "question-26":{
      "question":"What is a Binary?",
      "answer":"String of 1s and 0s",
      "choices":[
         "String of 1s and 2s",
         "String of -1s and 0",
         "String of 1s and 0s",
         "String of 1 and 2"
      ]
   },
   "question-27":{
      "question":"A ________ is a procedure or formula used for solving a problem",
      "answer":"Algorithm",
      "choices":[
         "Algorithm",
         "Pseudocode",
         "Program",
         "Computer"
      ]
   },
   "question-28":{
      "question":"Is a formal language comprising a set of strings that produce various kinds of machine code output",
      "answer":"Programming language",
      "choices":[
         "Programming language",
         "Binary",
         "Pseudocode",
         "None of the above"
      ]
   },
   "question-29":{
      "question":"Below are programming languages except ______",
      "answer":"JAV script",
      "choices":[
         "JAV script",
         "PHP",
         "C",
         "Python"
      ]
   },
   "question-30":{
      "question":"Below are the importance of programming in our everyday life except ______",
      "answer":"Hacking",
      "choices":[
         "Automation",
         "Hacking",
         "Communication",
         "Knowledge"
      ]
   }
}